This is it I've found it at last    The forbidden treasure of the ancient sorcerers  Hahahahaha! Hahahahaha    Hahahahaha!!! My dear prince! Are you going to the city to play cards again!? You are of royal blood! Walking the city streets dressed as a commoner       Have you no shame!? Quite frankly, I'm embarrassed!  <Run away> <Keep listening>    bcpThe Pharaoh has gotten wind of your activities    And he's quite concerned!  t<Run away> <Keep listening>    b pI realize I'm to blame for teaching you the card game    But you overindulge, my prince!  t<Run away> <Keep listening>    b pIt is high time you put aside this ridiculous pastime and focus on your studies   t<Run away> <Keep listening>    b bIt is wrong to worry the Pharaoh and the Queen so much! Please, dear Prince    Return to your room   e   "  / e3Wait! Stop, my prince!  e"Drat! He's gone   e Prince   w  You've returned    It is well into the night    Please return to the palace  Dear prince    If you still wish to play cards       then try your hand against me  If you lose, you must return to your room  I'm sure you'll find me a worthy opponent   t<Duel> <Pass>   L! !Ho ho ho  My dear prince    I taught you the game  You don't really think you're going to win, do you? Prepare yourself!  y  ue       iANow, then, young man    Go to your room! Ahem    please   t<Don't go> <Go>    AvA e3Wait! Come back!mph    You are wise to heed me  The hour is late  Sleep well, my prince   e   "  / e3Wait! Come back here!ou won    T'would seem that I taught you well    You've grown strong  You've won fair and square  As promised, you may go  I've nothing more to say     ve kmmm    T'would seem I've won  Many days have passed since I taught you the game    But you've still much to learn  Now, please    Return to the palace!e Have you played enough, my prince? I haven't told you this, but there's a story that goes with those cards    Would you be interested in hearing it?  t<Yes> <No>    I7SThen, listen well    Today, the Yu-Gi-Oh card deck is used simply as an entertaining pastime  But long ago, the cards were an invaluable magic aid for drawing out sorcerous powers   b  e  it z   b  3     z  tMagic-users were able to use their powers and summon the forces depicted on the cards  Some built kingdoms  Others waged wars   But the battles between mystics grew in intensity       until finally the use  of magic was forbidden  Now, only the cards remain in our kingdom  They are a reminder of those bygone days of magic     l  3  ie  e And so, Prince   w    Remember this tale when next you face an opponent with your deck  Never forget that humankind once overstepped its bounds and walked the path of destruction   :" k see    Go then, but try to be back at a decent hour     e  khere's nobody around      > a I've been waiting for you      w  Jono was also here a few minutes ago  But he's gone now    How about a duel?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    E M YOkay    I'll see you later   a  j,  w O  M  M a How about one game?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    Eu, Y a Aren't you ready to go yet?  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   u, YI'll see you later   a  F  H  D   !D j, C Y'know, there's some kinda festival goin' on in the town plaza  But we'd rather play games right here, like we always do  Wanna take me on? C'mon    let's play a game    " a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    R O+Y C Wanna take me on? C'mon    let's play a game   a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    R O+Y C Play again? I just lost to you a minute ago    Gimme some time to plan my strategy   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    O+Y  w Y  W 4 eW gO N Hey  Did you find yourself any rare cards? I managed to find a pretty good card myself! If you want it, you'll have to beat me  But if you lose, you'll have to give me one of yours   4" a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   j< W+Y N If you win, I'll give you my card  If you lose, you'll give me one of yours   a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   j< W+Y N Whoa    That's enough for today  If I lose again, I'll run out of cards   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    W+Y  w E  H )  H mH B You talkin' to me, boy? I got better things to do  Unless ya wanna challenge me     )" a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    < M+Y B You wanna play some cards?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    < M+Y B I think I've had enough, boy    It ain't no fun losin'!  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    M+Y  w F  a Hey, did you know that there's a festival going on in the town plaza? Come on! Let's check it out! I'll bet we'll find Jono there!  b  y  c#   0Hey, did you know that there's a festival going on in the town plaza? Come on! Let's check it out! I'll bet we'll find Jono there!  b  y  c#   0Okay, let's play! Hope you're not a sore loser!  y  ut     uch! Looks like I lost  Oh well    I'll play you again when I get a little better   vt t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   u,+YI won! I won! I think that's the first time I beat you,   w! I hope you didn't just let me win   kay, let's play!  y  uo     ell, well    Let's play again sometime     vo t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    O+YWhattya think? Not bad, eh?ll right, let's play!  y  ui     ou won    I guess I owe you a card   vi t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    W+YYes!!! I win!!! That means I get one of your cards! Right?kay, boy  Let's play!  y  un     mph! I reckon I lost    Looks like this just isn't my day     vn t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    M+YWell, boy    It looks like I won  Just leave one of your cards right there   t Geez    Who does that mage think he is anyway!? I gotta admit, though    that guy was real tough    Hey,  w, How about a game until that guy comes back?  t<Duel> <Pass>    G LAll right! Let's do it! I may have lost the last game    But I ain't lost my touch!  y  ua     eez,   w! You whipped me! Y'know    you are good! Do me a favor and beat that mage, willya?  va BNWhat's wrong,   w? You can do better than that! If that's your best, you'll never beat that mage!Fraid of starting off on the wrong foot, eh? I can understand that  Let's wait for the mage  Y'know, the guy's real tough    Listen  I play here day in and day out  And you know I'm pretty good    Fact is, there ain't too many duelists I can't beat  But that mage    Man   ! He's good! I didn't have a chance! Listen,   w    Don't underestimate the guy  I know you're good  But don't get sloppy     BNThere he is    He's back   t  - Look at that     ia #           t  5 He's got his own groupies    Do me a favor and whip the guy   5  & Do it,   w!  &  l it  o I do not know how good you are    But I hope you will entertain me  I will have you know that I enjoy a good game    Do not disappoint me!  y  us   "     I cannot believe I lost     z  o But    wait a moment  You    you are    Hmmm    I see    Enough  That is all for today  I have a feeling our paths will cross elsewhere    'Til then    I bid you farewell   z  o  vs  ?You lose, boy! You'll need better cards than that if you wish to beat me!twYou did it!   w  Didja see the look on his face!? You were great!!!  tO af  w    You're just too good!  tD aO"I bid you farewell"    Hah! What a loser!  LP  w, Well, what now? You still got some time?  t<Play> <Go outside>    P P a Okay! Why don't we play a quick game?  t<Duel> <Talk to someone else>   4U -Yeah? Well, come around again any time    We'll be here t Hey,   w! You're back! Wanna play?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   4U F -  w t It's gettin' pretty late,   w  Wanna play another match?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   4U F -Right  See ya around   kay  Catch ya later      -  w t  -  a You did pretty good back there    w  You know, maybe someday I'll be as good as you,   w   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   :z FSee you soon!ight  See ya around      w t  -  a I think I'll be heading home    What with the festival and all, I lost track of the time   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   :z F a  6 eK C That was some duel    I never saw anything like that before! How's 'bout giving me a chance? C'mon, let's play a game     a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   tx K K C Listen    I need a break  Let's play tomorrow   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    K KBe seein' ya    w $  j N Did you manage to get any rare cards? I'll play you for them if you want to   a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    xcj KSee you next time! w B Ya wanna play me? Listen, boy  I learned how good ya were the last time we played  I don't like losin'!  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   8-5U  w B If yer lookin' for that kid ya beat, he went home  I ain't gonna play no more  Why don't ya go home     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   8-5UBye kkay, let's do it!  y  ua     eez    You're just too good!    or maybe I'm just no good   va t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    - UWow! It looks like today's my lucky day!   w kay    Let's play!  y  uo     m    I can't seem to win  I think it's time I came up with another strategy   vo 6" t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>    K UWhattya think? Not bad, eh?lright, let's play!  y  ui     eez    You're just too good    I'm going home    I'll see you around   1  vi $" t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   cj UI did it! I won! I'll take that card!  V0Lots of people are gathered at the town plaza       but there's nothing of interest ooks like the festival's over  Not many people around       and there's nothing of interest R  qThe festival's in full swing       but there's nothing of interest ix  m"  b Wow    there're lots of people around  Look, the mages are about to start their procession     b  a  iqe b  & Awesome       but kinda spooky, too  This must be the work of that detestable high mage, Heishin  When I was a kid, it used to be more wholesome  Even the attitude of the mages have changed for the worse    What's our world coming to   ?  &  ix  a Want to go someplace else?  b  a  i   b  & Look! It's Jono! I can't believe it, but  he's dueling over there!  &  b  i0e 5 I    I lost     5  / I believe I have wasted my efforts on an insignificant speck   /  5 Say what!  5  / Forgive my choice of words  You were    mildly entertaining   /  & Hey! Jono!  &  5 Teana and   w     5  iq  t  &  tOWhat's going on?  &  tDWhaddaya think? Ain't it obvious?  tO & You lost     &  tDDon't be so blunt! I didn't lose    I had a setback     t  o I grow weary of this insect    Is there not one among you that is worthy of my attention?  oO 5 Man! The nerve of this guy!  5  & Hey,   w    Why don't you challenge him? After all, you're the best duelist I've ever seen! I'll bet you can beat him!  &  5 Yeah,   w! Do it! Show him who's boss around here!  5  oDHello    Are you my next victim?  t<Duel> <Pass>    1 ZI hope you are better than the last one  Come! Let us duel   oO 7 Master Seto! Master Heishin calls for you   7  oDI see    So be it  The duel is postponed  Am I correct in assuming that you frequent the town's duel field?  oO 5 That's right   5  oDThen wait there    I shall grace you with a visit  Seto is my name  Remember it     o  t Can you believe that guy!? A mage with attitude!!!  tO & Yeah    A real charmer   &  tDI got a feeling   w  will put him in his place  Won't ya, buddy? C'mon, let's look around and then head for the duel field   t   " y  plh! The coward shows his true colors    Why am I not surprised? You insects are all alike     oO 5 Hold on!   w  just doesn't want to face you here!  5  oDIs that so     oO 5 There's a duel field where we usually play  That's the place for a real battle!  5  oDThe town's duel field     oO 7 Master Seto! Master Heishin calls!  7  oDI see    So be it  Duty calls    The duel field, is it? Wait there and I will grace you with my presence  Seto is my name  Remember it     o  t Can you believe that guy!? A mage with attitude!!!  tO & Yeah    A real charmer   &  tDSorry,   w    I know you didn't want to duel the guy  But he called you a coward,   w! I couldn't let him get away with that! C'mon let's go to the duel field and wait for the guy!  t   " y  pln These hallowed halls are protected by High Mage Heishin! Commoners are not allowed! Begone with you!6 Where is Seto?  6  $ Must we be kept waiting!?  $  * Where can he be at a time like this!? T'would seem Master Heishin's favorite chooses to mock us     *  > Master Heishin does make much of Seto's capabilities       though he is but a child   >    I believe we've waited enough  Let us go  Master Heishin awaits us         " kello there!e Well, it's about time! Go on now! Off to your room!  e   / ii  e I really hope you're ready to call it a day     b  e  y   / ite b  3 Sometimes I wonder if the prince does this just to annoy me     3    Lord Simon Muran! We've got trouble! Th-the High Mage    The High Mage Heishin and his men    They wield a strange power    They're invading the palace!!!     eD 3  m  What!?  3  eO   I think it's sorcery, my lord! I'm afraid there's naught we can do to fend them off        eD 3 Where's the High Mage now!?  3    In the Palace Hall, my lord!     i   3 Heishin    Heishin! What could that dog have in mind?  3  e  io     3         Wha    What the     l 3  s It's good to see you again, Simon Muran     sO 3 You dare to revolt    Are you mad!?  3  sDMad   ? Me? I don't think so    I've but come to claim my throne   sO 3 Your throne!?  3  sDYes, my throne  For I now have the 'Power'     sO 3 The 'Power'    No    It cannot be     3  sDI see recognition in your eyes  But then we both draw our roots from our sorcerous forefathers     sO 3 The power of darkness   !?  3  sDThat's right  I've discovered the forbidden treasure     b  s  iae b Here! Taste the forbidden power of darkness!!!   : ii  g<  g>  c#  k!?  h Prince   w! The High Mage Heishin has invaded the palace! This place is too dangerous! We must leave at once!  h  b  y  cl  m   ioe b    No        / Prince   w    Did you hope to escape me?      We meet again       All right men    Away with this servant! I wish to speak with the prince   /  oO 7 By your command!  7    Prince   w!     7 Be quiet and come with us!  7  oD in  o Why do you flee?   w  Heishin already holds the King and Queen captive  Running away would only provoke Heishin to end their lives    Is that what you want? Well    I'll tell you what I want  Something that only one of royal blood would know       the location of the Millennium Item  Tell me where it is and I'll spare the King and Queen! You know where it is! So    tell me!  t<Refuse> <Tell>   v(a(Good    Now, talk!  6(Don't take me for a fool! You know where it is!!!  6( oO : My prince   !  :  oDSimon Muran!  o  iie : Dear prince    Here is the Millennium Item    Take it    take it and run!!!  :   w gets Millennium Puzzle!  in  l You must keep this treasure from falling into the hands of these vermin!!! The treasure is the final key to unlocking the seal to great power  Should it fall in the hands of the wicked, it would mean armageddon     lO / Well, well    You couldn't have brought it at a better time  Hand the key over to me right now, and I might help the two of you escape from Heishin   /  lOIgnore this cur! He wags his tail at Heishin's command! He's not to be trusted! Leave him to me, my prince! You must escape!  lO / Out of my way, old man!  /  lOGo, my prince! Run!  t<Run> <Stay>   z$Z$ b  y  c#   $Listen to what I say    Get out of here!  t<Run> <Stay>   z$Z$ m   l  in  b  s Do not move! You are mine! I see you've found them, Seto  Well done   sO / Yes, my lord     /  sDYou didn't think you'd escape me, did you? There's no point in resisting  Admit your defeat       and hand it over  Give me the Millennium Item!!!  sO : Only one option remains, my prince  You must do battle with Heishin  Challenge him to a duel with your cards and the Millennium Item!  :  t<Duel> <Pass>   <> > sDA wasted effort, boy! You lack the power to defeat me!  y  ur  n- : My dear prince! You must confront him! The Millennium Item will unleash the dark powers of your cards  Face him! You must defeat Heishin!  :  t<Duel> <Pass>   <> >Foolish child! You've wasted my time! If you insist on keeping the Millennium Puzzle, I'll just rip it from your lifeless fingers!  b  vr s  ine m   b  X !!! Out of my way, old man! Or else     X  : My prince! Shatter the Millennium Puzzle    You must not hand it over to this vile creature!  :  X Out of my way, old man! Get your hands off me!  X  : Prince    The puzzle       don't give them the puzzle     :  t<Don't shatter the puzzle> <Shatter the puzzle>   s<   ya ise gL  X No!!!  X  b  c   k: I beg you    the puzzle       shatter it     :  t<Don't shatter> <Shatter>   s<  Not bad, boy  But you're wrong if you think I'm beaten!  ur  n- b  er  w     eO!?  eDThank goodness! You've awoken! We're inside the Millennium Puzzle  To be precise, your soul is now sealed within the puzzle  I'm sorry, my prince  But this was the only way I could save you and the puzzle  I couldn't allow you to simply hand over the puzzle to the likes of Heishin  The power of darkness that Heishin sought to unravel could only lead to destruction  One day, when someone puts the puzzle together again, you will live to walk among men  Until that day comes    Sleep, my prince  I'm sure there is someone out there destined to assemble the Puzzle  In the end, that person and the Millennium Puzzle will guide you back to our world  Now rest, dear prince    Close your eyes     y  b  e   8 cc  i   b  ) Hey! Yugi! Wake up, Yugi!  )    Huh   ?     ir  m"  u You dozed off, fella!  uO   Really   ? Sorry        uDWhat's the matter? So nervous you couldn't sleep last night?  uO   I    had    a dream        uDYou were dreaming!? Man! Nothing fazes you, does it? C'mon  It's time for the opening ceremony  Let's go   u    (               )        b  y  m-  ii     b          l < Welcome to Yu-Gi-Oh! World Tournament, sponsored by the Kaiba Corporation! We're now at the TOWN OF DOMINO where selected duelists have gathered to decide who is number one!   <  ) This is it, Yugi   )    Yeah        b  ii     L  b The battles are about to begin    But before we start, there are a few rules to explain    Tournament rules are divided between the preliminaries and the finals  For example     L  ) Who cares about the rules  All you gotta do is keep winning! Right, Yugi?  )    Huh? Yeah  I guess so        L    and now, a few words from our sponsor, Mr  Kaiba!  L  m I thank you for joining us in deciding the king of kings    Today we duel to decide  who is the Game Master    the ultimate duelist! And I, too, am intent upon winning that honor     5  mOThat Kaiba gets on my nerves! If anybody puts him out of the tournament, I hope it's me! Yugi, I'm hoping to face you in the finals    Okay?  )    Sure!     m  L All right then, ladies and gentlemen! May the best man win! Let the duels begin!!!  b  L  ki, Yugi! I'm working part-time at this card shop during the tournament  What do you want to do?ood luck!  b  k  y     m   ih  < Preliminary Match #1 Yugi vs Rex Raptor!  <  g It's been awhile, Yugi    Guess you're gonna be watching me in the finals!  y  uh     vhYou    You beat me!!! I don't believe it!!!  U  bO cM  kahaha! It looks like the best man won    ME!!! Too bad, kid!!!ooking good, Yugi  Looking good! What do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Preliminary Match #2 Yugi vs Weevil Underwood!  <  y Hehehe    It's only fair to tell you    You ain't got a chance My army of insects will make mincemeat out of you!  y  ul     vlI lost    I LOST!!! My army of insects    Defeated by the likes of you     x  bO cM  karharhar!!! I'm a winner! I'm a winner! And you    You're a loser! Take a hike, loser! Buzz off!!! hear you're doing pretty well! What do you want to do?b  y  k  ih  m   < Preliminary Match #3 Yugi vs Mai Valentine!  <  w You should have quit before you faced me  You're going to regret it!  y  u      v I guess I lost    Oh well    I suppose I'll simply wish you luck!  q  bO cM  ky    That was easy    And I thought you were good!ou play a tough game, Yugi! What do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Preliminary Match #4 Yugi vs Bandit Keith!  <  f Long time no see    I came to bury you, Yugi    Get ready for a thrashing!  y  ud     vdI    I   yai   yai Me    The Card Professor    Beaten by this    this kid!  0  bO cM  kisten, kid  You didn't have a chance  I'm just tooooo good! heard you made the finals! That's great! Keep it up! Now, what do you want to do?b  y  k  m"  iy  u Hiya Yugi! Hear you're winning     uO   Yeah  How about you?     uDMe? Well, I ain't been eliminated yet! Maybe this time I will face you in the finals!!!  uO   I hope so! But     yt!!!     uDHuh? What's wrong, Yugi?  uO   Over there    It's Shadi        uDWhat!?  u  m3  c We meet again, Yugi   cO ) What're you doin' here? You lookin' for something?  )  cDI was summoned by Yugi's Millennium Item     cO   The Millennium Puzzle?     cDThat is correct  My own Millennium Item is reacting as if it wants to be here    Here and now  I believe that every last Millennium Item is gathered here at the tournament  My mission is to discover the secret of these Items  That is what brought me here   cO   Shadi    I had a weird dream about the Millennium Puzzle  There was another guy like me in the dream, locked in the puzzle    in another world  It was a really strange dream!     cDI see    That might have something to do with Yami Yugi    your doppelganger   cO   My doppelganger        cDYugi    Have you ever thought about meeting your dark twin?   cO   Me? Meet him?     ) And how's he gonna do that?  )  cDWe can use my Millennium Key to open your mind, Yugi  By delving deep into your mind, you can probably meet the other you that lies within  Yami Yugi was born from the power of the Millennium Puzzle  He emerges from within you  The dream you had    maybe he is trying to tell you something    I think this might be the time to meet him and talk     cO       I see what you're saying  I'll go see him if you're willing to help me      cD yeOkay    Here, touch my Millennium Key   b  c  ire b  ( Now close your eyes    Relax    Open your mind     (  b     m*  is  b    This is    my mind        dr dO   And you    are me    This is the first time I've met you    It's so    strange    I can see inside your mind  Don't need words    I can understand you       just by facing you            You want to return    back to your own world       I want to help    What do I have to do   ?     b  d  ihe b    A    card   ?  b  d  is  b  dOThe face    It's blank     d Wait! What is this card!?     y  b     m"  iy  b    !!     u Yugi? Are you alright?  uO   Uh    yeah      u  c Did it work? Did you meet him?  cO   I met him    But    we only spoke briefly    He told me he was a prince trapped in the puzzle    a long time ago  He said he had to get back to his own world    He asked me to help him get back  But I don't know how        ) Yugi? What's that you got in your hand?  )    Huh?  b  c  ige b This card   ! He gave me this card in my mind's world! He told me to use it to free him    to send him back to his own world!     ) What is it, Shadi?  )  iy  c I'm afraid I don't know    But it probably has something to do with the Millennium Item   cO   Six blank cards    I don't get it        c  u It's time to head back  Why don't we think on this later  We got some duels to fight   u     b  y  m   ih  b  < Match #1 of the Finals! Yugi vs Shadi!  <  c Yugi    We were drawn to battle by our Millennium Items  We were destined to duel!  y  uu     vuIt seems I've lost    Hm?  b  c  iye b  ( What the   ?! My Millennium Key and Millennium Scales!!!  (  gB  b  iwe b  ( They've been drawn into the cards    So this is why the Millennium Items were drawn to each other this day     (  ih  c Yugi, it seems your friend has summoned the Items together to absorb them into these cards   c  bO c>  khat's wrong, Yugi? Is that the best you can do? You can't lose! You're the Chosen One of the Millennium Puzzle! hear you're doing great! Keep it up! What do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Match #2 of the Finals! Yugi vs Bakura!  <  p It's odd    I had no intention of joining in this tournament    But my Millennium Ring    It called me to battle         cp  p3Good to see you, Yugi! It's high time we proved who the real Game Master is!!!  y  um     vmGuess I won't be claiming the Game Master title     b  p  ife b  a What in the   !?  gB  b  ipe b My Millennium Ring! It's being sucked into a card!  a  ih  p The ring    it   used    me    Thanks, Yugi    I'm now free of the Millennium Ring   p  b  c>  khat's it! Game Over! You just haven't got what it takes to win!eep focused, Yugi    Think    WINNER! Now, what do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Quarterfinal Match! Yugi vs Pegasus!  <  b Well, well    Yugi Boy  You've come a long way  But now it's time to lose   y  uc     vcDefeat can be bitter     b  2  ibe b  + Oh dear!  gB  b  ike b I don't believe it! My Millennium Eye     +  bO c>  kugi Boy    Victory is so sweet! You were foolish to challenge me   ne more duel, Yugi! And then it's the final battle! What do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Semifinal Match Yugi vs Isis!  <  P It's my pleasure to face you in battle, Yugi  But only one will walk away victorious    ME!!!  y  ug     vgHow    How could I lose     b  "  i!e b  8 !!!  gB  b  iAe b What   ? My Millennium Necklace    It's being drawn into a card!?  8  bO c>  kh my! I believe I won    Didn't I? I heard you were strong    But not strong enough!!!ou made it to the final! I'm rooting for you!!! What do you want to do?b  y  k  m   ih  < Well, this is it!!! Our finalists are the amazing Kaiba       and the undefeated Yugi!!!  <  m I thought I might be facing you, Yugi    My Millennium Rod is the final item    But the Rod whispers to me that I must defeat you  Yugi! Prepare to lose!!!  y  uy     vyThis cannot be    Me   ? Defeated   ?            b  j  ive b    What the   !? Light   ! So bright   !  gB  b  iDe b My Millenium Item    drawn into    into a card!?       HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!! Yugi!!! I've waited for this day!!! This is a day I will never forget!!! HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!y  iOe   I now have all the cards with the Millennium Items        b  is     b  gt M       oe l  w    Is this what you wanted   ?  b  ker  w    You've done it! Now you can go back to your own world  You have that boy to thank for this    Yugi    If I may be so bold, I believe the boy represents what you are to be  Now, with the Millennium Items pulling at each other over time    The portal to our world can be opened   b  e  iWe b  3 Heishin now has six of the Millennium Items and rules over an expansive realm  Using his items, he has managed to unleash a portion of the powers of darkness  He has placed each item in temples located at each conquered area to protect his holdings  Prince   w    You must retrieve all the Millennium Items    And seal them away once and for all  The locations of the temples containing the Millennium Items can be found in the ruins     3  b  e  is  b My time has come    I have done all that I can do  My flesh is no more    These will be my last words to you,   w  The rest is up to you  May success be yours     ye e   " b  k c* hat do you want to do?ade it back    This looks like the ruins of a temple  There's nobody here   ooks like the ruins of a temple   here's nobody here     t<Enter> <Don't enter>     n  ip  F   Everything's been destroyed     A Who are you!? No one's allowed here! Out! Get out!  t<Duel> <Pass>   k   You dare to resist me! I'll teach you a lesson you'll never forget!  y  uw   g vwYou know your cards well, boy    I underestimated you     A    Fool! You didn't stand a chance against me, boy!ow    Get out of here!!!  khis room    it used to be  Simon's room     > P  * 6  P Everything's been destroyed   t<Search> <Don't search>       !  iYe  w discovers an ancient papyrus! It's a map to the Forbidden Ruins  This map should lead to the Forbidden Ruins     >" k think I'll go back   kverything's destroyed    There's nobody around   obody's here    It looks abandoned     5 Hey!   w!  5   " t Wow! You're alive!!! I never dreamed that I'd see you again,   w! I still can't believe it! Y'know, I was really surprised when I first learned that you were actually a prince! It's good to see you! I never dreamed that you'd manage to get away!!!   w    This place has changed since you disappeared  It's a sad situation, but the duels still go on    at a secret location nearby  C'mon, I'll take you there  Let's go!  t    Nobody's here    It looks abandoned        >         ! Who's that!? None may enter the Valley of the Kings! Leave!  !3!? My    my prince! You're alive!!!  !"I am Sadin! For generations, my family has guarded this valley! Please rest assured that I've kept Heishin out of this valley, my prince  I'm sorry about what happened to the Pharaoh and the Queen    The vile ones have taken over this land  But, now    Now that you're alive       there is hope once again for everybody   t The remains of the Pharaoh and Queen are not here    I'm sorry to say that Heishin wouldn't allow it  Is there anything else you want?  t  t<Go to the Forbidden Ruins> <Leave this place>       <Leave this place>*"The Forbidden Ruins? Simon Muran said it was here? I'm sorry, but I've never seen such a place    There are so many tombs for royalty, nobody knows which tunnel leads to where    If there's a Forbidden Tomb, I don't know where it is    My apologies, good prince    Anything else, my prince?  t  a<Go to parents' tomb> <Go to Forbidden Ruins> <Leave this place>   i     <Leave this place>f you require my services, you can always find me here    " k! How can I be of help, my prince?  t<Go to Forbidden Ruins> <Leave this place>        *"My apologies, good prince  I know not where the Forbidden Room is located  Perhaps if you had some sort of clue from Master Simon     t<Go to Forbidden Ruins> <Leave this place>       I see    If you require my services, you can always find me here ! Can I be of service?  t<Give Map> <Leave this place>   F   So Master Simon did leave behind a clue to the whereabouts of the ruins    Let me see    Right! I know where this is  Please, follow me     !  y    If you require my services, you can always find me here ! Is something wrong, my prince?  t<Go to Forbidden Ruins> <Return>       I see    Be careful, my prince   !  b  y  m     What is it you wish to know? Well, if you need me    you know where to find me   ! b  y  m   iv  b  t Here ya go    This is where we set up our new dueling grounds    w, the mages spent days trying to find out where you might've run off to  When we said we had no idea, they destroyed our old dueling grounds    That's why me and the Card Shop owner moved the dueling grounds down here   tO &   w! You're alive!  &  ae aO tDWhat'd ya expect!?   w isn't dumb enough to be caught!  tO aDYou know, it's a miracle that you managed to elude them   aO tDYeah  Those guys've taken over the entire kingdom  They do as they please    control everything    They wield some kinda strange magic    Nobody can stand up to 'em! The way things're going, we'll have to live down here for the rest of our lives      w    Feel like dueling? It beats moping around just worrying about things     a<Duel with Jono> <Duel with Teana> <Decline>   M O $     tO aDI think I may surprise you!  y  up     aO tDOkay    Maybe next time  The old man runs his Card Shop down here  Drop in when you got the chance   tO aDSee you around!  # Haven't seen you awhile    As you can see, I'm still around      " t<Card Shop> <Dueling Grounds>       What can I do for you?  t<Card Shop> <Dueling Grounds>        b  r  iv  b    Hello  What can I do for you?t         a     U    q    V    J h  1    L  q    V    J    1       V    J    1       J    1       1       U    q    V    J    1   Hiya,   w  You're looking good     $ Wanna duel?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>          % L  %"Hey! I heard all about it! You beat a high mage!? You've got the mages and their soldiers in a state of shock! That's really cool      w!  a<Duel with Jono> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>          %"  w! We got some trouble! Seto and the mages came here while I was gone    They took off with Teana! They want you,   w    They figure they can drag you out with Teana as bait!!! C'mon,   w  Let's go to the Shrine and rescue Teana!  t   " A      "Man, that was rough! Well, at least we've got Teana back    Y'know, those guys were acting really strange     a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>          U '  q z  V /  J >  1 9     q L  V L  J L  1 L  9  V L  J L  1 L  9  J L  1 L  9  1 L  9 One more high mage to go, eh?   w, Be careful    We're depending on you   a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>         You did it!!! You beat every last one of 'em! Now all you gotta do is defeat Heishin and Seto, right? I knew you could do it! When you become king,   w    and things're back to normal, I hope you don't forget we're friends       real good friends   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>        t  -  a         p  U    q    V    J    1    L What's up,   w? Feel like a duel?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>     F      L   "I was told you beat a high mage    You've got the other mages scared! Well done,   w!  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>     F        Thanks for helping me      w    I just knew you'd come and rescue me    "  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>     F    U    q    V    J    1       q L  V L  J L  1 L     V L  J L  1 L     J L  1 L     1 L    Beat one more high mage, and you'll be facing Heishin next  Luck be with you,   w!  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>     F   Now, all that's left is Heishin    I hear Heishin is a very powerful duelist    Be careful    w    I'm betting you come out a real winner!  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   F    a  F  C            U f  q f  V f  J f  1 f      w    Nice to see you're still alive  Prince   w    so you're royalty, eh? Feels real strange, after all we've been through    Everything seems so unreal    That's why we keep dueling  It's all we've got to keep us sane  Hope you don't mind if we treat you like we did before  C'mon, let's play!   "  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   g     Hey,   w! How 'bout a game?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   g            "Have you noticed that the mages've been down, lately?    It's all because of you,   w    C'mon, let's play!  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   g      U    q    V e  J m  1 k     q    V    J    1    k  V    J    1    k  J    1    k  1    k Hah! You whipped those high mages! Fantastic! I hear you got one more to go    Luck be with you!  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   g     Awright!!! I heard you beat every last one of those high mages!!! Great news!!! Oops! I guess once you put all of 'em away, I'll have to be calling you King   w  Best I watch my tongue, eh? I just hope you'll never forget us once you're the Pharaoh     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>        C  #  N    a       U    q    V    J    1        "It's very difficult to get rare cards these days    Really tough  Well, do you want to play?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   1 y   You want to duel with me?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   1 y          "You beat a high mage!? Maybe things'll go back to normal around here! When it does, maybe I can collect rare cards like I used to!!! Do you want to duel?  a<Duel> <Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   1 y    U    q    V a  J g  1 A     q    V    J    1    A  V    J    1    A  J    1    A  1    A You really did it!!! Keep it up and maybe things will turn back to normal     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   y   You did it! You showed those mages! When you become Pharaoh, don't forget us, okay?  t<Talk to someone else> <To outside>   y    N  1  B    "       U    q    V    J    1    3   "It's been a while, boy    I've been here everyday  I've got nowhere else to go  Things've changed around here    Y'know, I've lost my interest in dueling these days    All I do now is come here to trade cards   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       How about it? Wanna trade cards with me, boy?  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>          i   "Not bad,   w    How's about giving me that rare card?  t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>        U O  q 0  V 4  J 8  1       q 3  V 3  J 3  1 3     V 3  J 3  1 3     J 3  1 3     1 3    Y'know    I think dueling isn't just winning and losing       collecting 'em can be just as much fun   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       Looks like there might be a chance for some peace again    Y'know, if things go back to normal, I think I'm gonna miss my life underground     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>        B  t  $  B  t     pc got a feeling today's my day!  y  uf     e warned! I'm good     y  up     in or lose    no hard feelings   y  uo     on't hold back    You'll be sorry if you do   y  ui     U    q    V    J    1       U g  q g  V g  J g  1 g  3 Man! I was so sure that I was gonna win this time! Looks like I'm just gonna have to try harder     vf t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       Geez    I won  You must be getting rusty   hew! You're just too good! I just can't win! I promise you it won't be so easy to beat me the next time we play     vf t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       What's wrong,   w? You can do better than that! If you play like that against the mages, they'll beat you silly! Keep your mind on the game!U    q    V    J    1       U C  q C  V C  J C  1 C  )  vpDarn! I lost    I know I played better than I've ever played before     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   F   Yessss! I win! I win! Not bad, right? I'll bet you're really surprised!vpOuch! I lost    Oh well    But then if I did beat the great   w, that's when I should be really worried   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   F   Wow!!! I won!!!   w    You'll have to do better than that to beat the high mage   U    q    V    J    1       U    q    V    J    1      Whew    I just can't win against you   vo t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       Finally! I finally beat you fair and square,   w! Looks like all my practice paid off!hew    I just can't win against you   voWell, thanks for the practice     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>       Well, well, well    I really did it    I beat you,   w! But if that's the case, who's going to save the world?U P  q P  V P  J P  1 P     U    q    V    J    1       viI lose    Looks like I'm going to need some stronger cards   t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   y   I won! I won! I can't believe it! I actually won with these cards!!!viI guess I lost    With these cards of mine, I'm not too surprised     t<Talk to someone else> <Go outside>   y   Whoa! I won!!! I'll bet you're not too happy about that! " b  i   b    Further on    You'll find the room marked on the map   m  Oh my        b  iA  b    I've heard stories about this place before    The ancient sorcerers    they hid the secrets of their magic within the Royal Tomb    It's rumored that some of the secrets were passed on to their descendents  So this is the place        ! There's a drawing on this wall depicting the past    And over there       some kind of map     t<Look at Map> <Look at Drawing>     8  <    <" !  iEe   This map    There's some kind of mark        / That drawing on the wall marks the location of the Millennium Items  And now, it reveals the spots in the temple where Heishin has hidden his Millennium Items  The mages will remain powerful as long as the Millennium Items remain in the temple       providing them with a source for their magic   yt /    You!     iA  m   o I followed you here  I've been searching for the Forbidden Ruins myself  I also believe that Heishin's found this place as well  With that drawing on the wall to guide him, he discovered the Millennium Items  He may be a mage, but he comes from a line of sorcerers  He plans to find all the Millennium Items so that he may rule over the world one day     oO   And why would Heishin's lackey tell us all this!?     oDWhy? You'll find out soon enough    But first, let's see what Prince   w is capable of  You now know where to find the high mages    If you're half the card master that you think you are, use your Millennium item and defeat them!  oO   We don't have to listen to you        oDI'm not talking to you, tomb keeper! I speak to your prince! Farewell!  o     ytHold it!  m      ! I smell a rat    Seto    He's Heishin's right-hand man  Why in the world would he want to help you? My prince, I advise caution  There is more to this than meets the eye   Y  t<Look at Map> <Look at Drawing>     8  a<Look at Map> <Look at Drawing> <Return>     8         b  !  i      b    It looks like a drawing of some sort of spell    Could this be describing one of the Forbidden items?      " b  !  iA  b  < Y     b  !  iEe b The map marks the locations of the Shrines where the Millennium Items are hidden   b  !  iA  b  < Y     b  !  i      b Looks like a drawing of an ancient spell     b  !  iA  b  < Y    Let us return     !  y  i!  m   ! I sense there may be more secrets hidden within that chamber    My prince    Be wary of the vile designs of Heishin and his minions  I will always be here for you  If you need me, all you have to do is call on me iA  a<Look at Map> <Look at Drawing> <Return>     Q    iEeThe map marks the locations of the temple where the Millennium Items can be found      i     It looks like the drawing of an ancient spell        b  y  m   i!  ! I shall be here if you need me, my prince   "  A Boy, this is a sacred temple of Lord Heishin    It is not for the likes of you! Begone! b  y  m   iO  b  5 This is it    This place gives me the creeps    To be honest, I don't really like being here  Seein' how there's no mage around to stop us, we can assume they're waiting for us  C'mon, let's go     5        b    ?         W       i0  ?  b It gives me great pleasure to welcome you fools to your own funeral!  ?O 5 Scram! We got bigger fish to fry!  5  ?D y  u,   g i0  ?  b Welcome    I hope you're prepared to meet your ancestors!  ?O 5 Not you guys again!?   w! Show 'em who's boss!  5  y  u,   g i0  ?  b Welcome    I hope you're prepared to meet your ancestors!  ?O 5 They just don't give up! We'll just have to take him out!  5  y  u,   g i0  ?  b Welcome    I hope you're prepared to meet your ancestors!  ?O 5 Y'know    I think we're lost     5  y  u,   g i0  ?  b Welcome    I hope you're prepared to meet your ancestors!  ?O 5 Not again! C'mon, let's take care of him!  5  y  u,   g   L         i        "You cannot hope to survive this labyrinth     v, Z  5 Look, ignore this guy     Let's move on!  5  t<Go right> <Go left>       Seto and Heishin    My masters will be pleased! Hahahahaha   ! "You cannot hope to survive this labyrinth     Z  5 C'mon, let's go! Teana's waiting for us!  5  t<Go right> <Go left>         "You cannot hope to survive this labyrinth     Z  5 Why do I get this feeling of deja vu   ? Which way do we go?  5  t<Go right> <Go left>         "You cannot hope to survive this labyrinth     Z  5 Man! These guys are everywhere!!! C'mon, let's keep moving!  5  t<Go right> <Go left>       You cannot hope to survive this labyrinth     Z  5 Look, let's try to pick a route that gets us somewhere     5  t<Go right> <Go left>        i0  5 I can't take much more of this     5  t<Go right> <Go left>        i0  5 Which way now?  5  t<Go right> <Go left>     x  i0  5 Everyplace looks the same! Where are we anyway!?  5  t<Go right> <Go left>        iV  5 I think we've finally made it    Let's go     5          i"e / So you've come at last     /  5 We're here for Teana!  5  X Hmmm  I never dreamed the prince would be alive    There is much to be said of the Millennium Puzzle's power    Actually, I should thank my lucky stars that the Puzzle still exists for me to take  Seto    Destroy the prince  Defeat him and I will make you guardian of the Puzzle   X  / I thank you, my lord  Leave his life in my hands     /  X That I shall    He is all yours! I will meet you back at the Dark Shrine   X  b  i3e b  / My, my    I am surprised that you passed the trials of the labyrinth     /  5 Are you kidding! We coulda done it with both hands tied behind our backs! Is that the best you can do?!  5  b  o  iW  b Ah, the hostage    You can have her back         w    I've been waiting for this chance to face you once again!!!  Z   w    You don't know how I've looked forward to facing you     Z There is no joy in simply trading the hostage for your item    The joy is in the battle,   w!  y  uD   "  vDNot bad    Not bad at all  At this rate, I doubt that the mages will be able to stop you    You win    Take the card and the girl  Till we meet again     o    Very disappointing    You haven't a chance against the mages if this is the best you can do  Your Millennium Item    It is mine to keep! Hahaha   t Teana    Are you okay?  tO & Uh, yeah    Thanks,   w    You too, Jono   &  tDLook  I've had enough of this place  Let's get outta here   t  y  iv  m   t Y'know, there's something strange about that Seto guy     tO & I know    It's like he didn't really want to beat   w at all  It's like he's got a different agenda     &  tDI know what you mean    Listen,   w    You be careful around that guy  He's dangerous i3e b  5 We've come for Teana!  5  / My, my    I am surprised that you passed the trials of the labyrinth     /  5 Are you kidding! We coulda done it with both hands tied behind our backs! Is that the best you can do?!  5  b  o  iW  b Ah, the hostage    You can have her back  I didn't use her as bait to take your precious item    I did it so I could guide you to Heishin's chambers  You'll find him in the temple ahead  Face him! Defeat him!  oO 5 Don't listen to him,   w! It's a trap!!!  5  oDDon't be a fool    I'm giving you an opportunity to defeat Heishin    Can you afford to ignore such a chance?  t<Go on ahead> <Ignore the chance>   r   You've made a wise choice, dear prince   oO 5 You wanna go on,   w? If that's what you wanna do, I won't stop you    But be careful, willya? We'll be waiting for you!  5  & Yes  We'll wait for you     &     5  oDf you don't go now, you'll never have another chance     t<Go on ahead> <Ignore the chance>   r    t<Go on ahead> <Ignore the chance>        iW  o Here    This is a secret passage    I'll open it for you      b  g     o  iRe b  / Heishin's Dark Shrine lies just up ahead    Along the way, you'll find mages that have sworn to protect him  It is wise to be cautious     /  b     j    q    V    J    1   You! Who are   ? Wait! You    you're    Prince   w   ! How did you get here!? It matters not    You won't be leaving alive!  y  ub  ig ou're finally here! I'm afraid I can't let you enter the Sea Shrine  It is our duty to protect the Millennium Items -- the source of our mystic power  This Sea Shrine will be your place of eternal rest! Prepare to lose!  y  ub  ig ou're back!? You won't get away this time!  y  ub  ig ou were a fool to hope to defeat us    Hahahaha   !o    It cannot be    You weren't meant to win    Secmeton    Forgive me     vb v  t<Proceed> <Return>       kb  iY  I  b I am the High Mage Secmeton    Since time immemorial, it has been our duty to protect the Millennium Items    And we shall never allow them to fall into your hands! Prepare to face my Sea Deck! Prepare to meet your doom! You shall pay dearly for your folly!  y  uk  iD  trust you've learned your lesson! Too bad it comes too late!vkYou    are    powerful    But you don't stand a chance against the power of Master Heishin!  I  b  m   i!e b   w gets the Millennium Necklace   cM   U d  V d  J d  1 d  q d       iY  c There's nobody at this shrine   x 2  U    V    J    1   Who!? You   !? Prince   w! It's a wonder you've made it this far! Too bad    You'll never leave here alive!!!  y  u!  eg elcome to the Forest Shrine    Unfortunately, you will be going no further than this  That's right    This is your final resting place    I'll make sure of that!!!  y  u!  eg ou! You won't be getting your hands on the Millennium item this day    I'll make sure of that!!!  y  u!  eg y Forest Deck is powerful indeed! How do you like the taste of defeat!? Hahaha   !!! am defeated    But you won't find our High Mage to be such easy prey     v! '  t<Proceed> <Return>       kb  iR  T  b I am the ruler of the forest    I am High Mage Anubisius! Here I stand to protect the Millennium Item entrusted to me by Lord Heishin    This is where the Millennium Item belongs  And this is where it will remain!!! It is our destiny to protect the item that powers our magic! Prepare to face my Forest Deck! Prepare to battle! And prepare to lose!!!  y  uA  eD oolish child    You gravely erred when you chose to face me!!!vANo    It cannot be    Master Heishin shall avenge me   ! I'll    see    you    in    in     T  b  m   i<e b   w gets the Millennium Key!!!  U d  V d  J d  1 d  q d       iR  c There's nobody at this shrine   0    q    U    J    1   Who!? You   !? Prince   w! I'm amazed you've made it this far! Too bad    You'll never leave here alive!!!  y  uv  ag  congratulate you    But you'll regret that you made it here to the Mountain Shrine! Ahead lies the resting place for a sacred Millennium Item  I am sworn to protect it with my life!  y  uv  ag ou are a fool to return here and face me    Prepare to lose!!!  y  uv  ag diot! Did you think to defeat a mage of the mountains?hat!? It cannot be    I don't believe it     vv S  t<Proceed> <Return>   H D kb  i>  M  b I am the protector of the mountains    High Mage Atenza    The Millennium Item you seek is under my protection  If you wish to have it, you must face the wrath of my mighty Mountain Deck! Prepare for battle!!!  y  uI  aD  told you once before    You couldn't win  You are a mere groundling       destined to wander the earth  And to be buried below it!!!vIHow could this be   ? Me   ? Defeated   ?  M  b  m   ife b   w gets the Millennium Ring!!!  U d  V d  J d  1 d  q d       i>  c There is nobody at this shrine   J r  2    q    V    U    1   Who!? You   !? Prince   w! I'm amazed you've made it this far! Too bad    You'll never leave here alive!!!  y  u'  tg ou've kept me waiting long enough    The Millennium items are the source of our mystic power    and will remain so! They shall never be yours!!! This Desert Shrine shall be your final resting place!!!  y  u'  tg o you've returned    You'll wish you hadn't  I'll show you why!!!  y  u'  tg oo bad Master Heishin isn't here to see your demise    Too bad   o    I cannot    lose    Not like this     v' ,  t<Proceed> <Return>       kb  i-  D  b I am High Mage Martis    Lord of the Desert  I am forsworn to protect the Millennium Item  It is my destiny to eliminate you!!! Let the desert be your grave    Defend yourself!!!  y  uT  tD his is your destiny    The desert embraces your remains   vTThe desert claims me this day     D  b  m   i>e b   w gets the Millenium Scales!  U d  V d  J d  1 d  q d       i-  c There's nobody at this shrine   #    q    V    J    U   Who!? You   !? Prince   w! I'm amazed that you've made it this far! Too bad    You'll never leave here alive!!!  y  uS  og ongratulations are in order for making it this far    But this is as far as you get  High Mage Kepura will not be bothered by the likes of you! Prepare to lose!!!  y  uS  og  w   ? You won't win this time!  y  uS  og ah! This is where it all ends for you! Hahaha    w    You'll regret this victory    For you'll be facing the power of High Mage Kepura     vS O  t<Proceed> <Return>     4 kb  iz  W  b I am the guardian of the plains    I am the High Mage Kepura  You are the protector of light    The owner of the Millennium Puzzle  Our Millennium Item is not for the likes of you    It must never be yours! The Millennium Item is  Master Heishin's and our key to world domination  First, I will defeat you    Then, I will take your Millennium Puzzle and offer it to Master Heishin  Prepare to defend yourself!!!  y  uM  oD ou actually hoped to face Master Heishin   ? Foolish child   vMSo    this    is the power of light    Heishin    my lord    I have failed you     W  b  m   ibe b   w gets the Millennium Eye!!!  U d  V d  J d  1 d  q d       iz  c There's nobody at this shrine   ky  m   o   w    You actually defeated the High Mages    All that remains is Heishin's Shrine of Darkness  But you can't go there directly  You must return    Go back to the Vast Shrine   o   " k " kb  y  m   iK  H Halt!!!  Ye HOYou are forbidden to proceed any further!  YO HDSo speaketh the Royal Mages Sebek the Powerful and     HO YDNeku the Skillful! This is where it all ends     Y  HDPrepare to lose!!!  y  uO  nD ahaha! We are the chosen duelists    The ultimate players    You didn't stand a chance    Hahaha!!!vOCurse you,   w    You've won for now    But Neku    He shall defeat you!!!  H  YeI never thought I'd see Sebek defeated    Let's see what you've got!!!  y  uW  nD mph! You met your match this day! And you thought to face Master Heishin    HAH!!!vWSo this    This is    your power    I underestimated you     Y  b  y  c>  kt's been some time since last we met, boy! I salute you for making it this far    But it all ends here  I haven't come this far to be beaten by a child!!!  y  uH  n- ow you know, boy    Now you know true power!!!idiculous    Me    Defeated by this    This child!!! No    I won't let it end this way     K  vH y  / Well done     ir    Now all the items have been gathered as one     /  b  ij  o  b Let us head for the Forbidden Ruins     b  o  y  ko  m    w    It's time to end this farce  I will now defeat you once and for all  And all the items will be mine! Don't look so surprised    I only helped you because I needed you for my plans  I served Heishin as his right-hand man in the hopes of stealing the Millennium Items one day  And then you came along  You found the temple, and you won each of the precious items       saving me the trouble of doing it myself!!! In short, you were nothing more than a pawn in my designs! I could never allow lowly humans such as you or Heishin to take those items    They belong to the highborn    They can only be held by a noble    One such as myself   b  o  ize b  / This place is home to my forefathers    The royal tomb of those who prospered wielding the dark power    Do you know why this place is called the Forbidden Ruins? It is because of    THIS!!!  /  b  g?  c>  ih     b        l / The Millennium Items represent a pact    an agreement for tapping the powers of darkness  The ancient kings and sorcerers gained supreme power from the Dark Lord    And now I intend to summon him    Here, to these very chambers    I will renew that pact, and regain the power to rule over all!!!  /  b  iU  o  b And now    the final battle! I will eliminate you once and for all  The items shall be mine!!!  y  uY   " ahahahahahaha!!! Finally    I have them all  Power shall be mine this day!!!   w    You have my thanks!vYNot like this    To come this close    And lose to you    Please    Not like this     z  kt<Destroy Items> <Don't destroy>   1 1  X Hold it right there!!!  X  iKe m  If you wish to let Seto live, hand over the Millennium Items   X Did you think me foolish enough to fall for this cretin's ploy? I've known he descended from the Dark Household for some time now  I closed my eyes to his treachery, and staged my defeat so I could discover his true intentions! Perhaps you thought me senile? Blind to your pitiful plans? Thanks to you, I now stand in the Forbidden Chamber that can only be opened by one of the Dark  Come    Hand over the items and I'll spare this fool      t<Hand over the items> <Refuse>       My dear boy    You try my patience!     X  / No     /  b  iU  s  b Hahah!!! I did it! They're mine at last!!! Now I can summon the DarkNite!!! You princes of a lost dynasty    You are privileged to see the birth of a new king! A new age! Come to me, Darkness!!! Grant me the power!!! Grant me the world!!!  b  y  s  ije b  cp  ge    b  c   m   E  iU  cH  b  EO X I welcome you dark one    Bound by your ancient pact    I command you to obey!!!  X  EDHeheheh    I return after thousands of years, and what do I find   ? You command me to what?  EO X Obey! You must obey    It's in the ancient pact!  X  EDI've made no pact with the likes of you    Why should I be compelled to obey you   ?  EO X The Items    The Millennium Items! I have them all!!!  X  EDThe Millennium Items? I see no items     EO X Of course you don't! I used them    I used them to summon you! And now you must honor the pact! You must obey me!!!  X  EDI weary of this conversation     EO X No    No!!! Don't! Doooooon't!!!  X  b  gN  E  iUe b  9 That's better    You look better as a card   9  X Help! Help meeeeeeee!!!  X  9 This is the noisiest card I've ever created       not to mention, the ugliest one, too  Frankly, it doesn't deserve a place in my deck     9  g>  iGe X Nooooooooooooooooo!!!  X  9 Oops     9  b  iU  E  b Long have I shared my power through the cards I've created    It is now time that I collected the price for my power  And the best place to start is with this miserable planet    these miserable creatures     EO /   w!!! Your deck! It still contains the Millennium Card    The card you used to return to this world    Use them! Use the cards to send that thing back     /  EDHeheheh    I think the two of you will be great additions to my personal deck     b  E  ixe b  9 What!?  9  / We still hold one card that represents our pact with you   /  b  E  iU  b I see that you do  But I don't  intend to go back empty-handed after coming all this way    I'll tell you what    I'll give you one chance  It's only fair that the course of our pact be decided with the cards  Beat me in a duel, and I will go home    quietly  Now, come on    Let's play     y  uE   * athetic!!! I should have known you were far too inferior to provide a challenge! Well, you know the rules    I won    And the world is mine! Heheh     E3Heheheheheheheheheheh!!! Heheheheheheheheheheh!!! Heheheheheheheheheheh!!! Heheheheheheheheheheh!!! Heheheheheheheheheheh!!! Heheheheheheheheheheh   vETh   this is not fair! Me   !? ME!? I cannot lose!!! I created the cards!!! No    No    I CANNOT LOSE!!!  b  E  R  b COME, BOY!!! ONE MORE TIME!!! ONE MORE GAME!!!  y  uR     ND THE WINNER IIIIIS    ME!!! YESSSSSS!!! THIS WORLD IS MINE!!! ALL MINE!!!vRNO! NOT AGAIN!!!  gC NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO  b  R  c#  b  c#         b  ie     b     c oe l     i   mD That day, Seto left the ruins    Never to be seen again   in     b       -tEgypt was unified once again under the rule of   w  To protect mankind, he ordered       the Forbidden Ruins to be buried    w became the greatest of pharaohs, bringing prosperity to all he ruled  The vile mages were no more  This was the tale of   w, he whom we call    "Yu-Gi-Oh"  l k      y w S                  e e e e t t t           t t tDaXa       a a a!oFo9o o   o oai      aiaiaiai oimiTiLi nfsLs rLshjl l l l l        l l l l lD U         :d d d dtuuuMuLu2u*u u u u u uem2m m m m m m m m,c c c c c c c cjg g g               g g g g g g7y y y y wSw        7w w w h h2l l lz      d dau u u m mHc c c ghy y,w w'f f fPp p pRb b b!k7k ko!V! ! ! A A A4v v vJI I Ie' ' ' 'BT T TxS S S+M Mz, , ,aDJD D D DNO O O O7W W W H H H9Y Y YTE E E EVR R R R < <i>)> > >:G GtLZL L LgC C C CXN NuB B B Bx? ? ?yP P PU- - -wF F Fmz z zeK K Kdj j j*U U U)x x xVq q q"0 0cV V V V 2 2 J J J J*# # #L1 1 1 12Q Q Q6Z Z Zj" " " "Q3 3 3O5 5 5h&4& & &
1
